kikolani.com 2019-03-31

# Privacy Policy

The privacy of visitors to [kikolani.com](https://kikolani.com/) is important.

At [kikolani.com](https://kikolani.com/), I recognize that privacy of your personal information is important. Here is information on what types of personal information this site receives and collects when you use and visit [kikolani.com](https://kikolani.com/), and how your information is safeguarded. I never sell your personal information to third parties.

 **Log Files**

As with most other websites, this site collects and uses the data contained in log files. The information in the log files include your IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP (internet service provider, such as AOL or Shaw Cable), the browser you used to visit our site (such as Internet Explorer or Firefox), the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site.

 **Email Addresses**

[Kikolani.com](https://kikolani.com/) will never sell or distribute your email addresses to other parties. Email addresses entered in this site via the contact form or comments form will only be used by the site owner to directly contact the email address owner via email or on social networks.

 **Cookies and Web Beacons**

This site does use cookies to store information, such as the information you previously used when filling out a comment form. 

We also use third party advertisements (affiliate links) on [kikolani.com](https://kikolani.com/) to support our site. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP , the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed. This is generally used for geotargeting purposes (showing New York real estate ads to someone in New York, for example) or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing cooking ads to someone who frequents cooking sites).

 **DoubleClick DART cookies**

We also may use DART cookies for ad serving through Googleâ€™s DoubleClick, which places a cookie on your computer when you are browsing the web and visit a site using DoubleClick advertising (including some Google AdSense advertisements). This cookie is used to serve ads specific to you and your interests (â€interest based targetingâ€). The ads served will be targeted based on your previous browsing history (For example, if you have been viewing sites about visiting Las Vegas, you may see Las Vegas hotel advertisements when viewing a non-related site, such as on a site about hockey). DART uses â€œnon personally identifiable informationâ€. It does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, telephone number, social security numbers, bank account numbers or credit card numbers. You can opt-out of this ad serving on all sites using this advertising by visiting <http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/dart_adserving.aspx>

You can choose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites. This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts.

Deleting cookies does not mean you are permanently opted out of any advertising program. Unless you have settings that disallow cookies, the next time you visit a site running the advertisements, a new cookie will be added.

AdSense Privacy Policy Provided by [JenSense](http://www.jensense.com/) and modified by [kikolani.com](https://kikolani.com/).
